Erol Bicer, Ph.D.Nuclear Engineer



- www.erolbicer.com
- +82-10-7497-0705
- South Korea
- R^G ResearchGate/Erol-Bicer
- GitHub/nucerl

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Turkish - Fluent

Korean — Conversational

SYSTEM CODES

RELAP5 | MARS-KS | SPACE

CONTAINMENT CODES

GOTHIC | CAP

SEVERE ACCIDENT

MELCOR

CFD CODES

OpenFOAM | CUPID

CODING LANGUAGES

PYTHON | MATLAB | FORTRAN | C++ | HTML/CSS

TOOLS

ERP | Microsoft Project | Trello |
Jira | Git | PCTRAN | SNAP |
Origin | Salome | DOS/UNIX |
ParaView | CATIA | Mathcad

PROFILE

I specialize in conducting comprehensive safety analyses for various types of nuclear power plants using advanced system and computational fluid dynamics codes. My experience encompasses successfully developing, leading, and completing international projects through effective collaboration with global teams.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FNC Technology Co., Ltd. 🛮

Manager

2023 - present | South Korea

Associate Manager

2019 - 2023 | South Korea

Assistant Manager

2016 - 2019 | South Korea

Bil-Plas Industry and Trade Co., Ltd., R&D Engineer

2013 − 2014 | Ankara, Turkey

EDUCATION

Nuclear Engineering, Ph.D., Seoul National University

2024 | Seoul, South Korea

Nuclear Power Plant Engineering, M.Sc., KINGS ≥ 2016 | Ulsan, South Korea

Nuclear Energy Engineering, B.Sc., Hacettepe University
2013 | Ankara, Türkiye

LATEST PROJECTS

[SMR] Small and Micro Modular Reactors Technology Analyses
Project Development and Management (APM)

[MSR] Development and Analysis of Fuel Salt Leakage Behavior in Discharge System Shell

Project Development and Management (APM)

[SMART] System-Integrated Modular Advanced Reactor Passive Containment Cooling System

[PGSFR] Prototype Gen-IV Sodium-Cooled Fast Reactor Analysis

[EUR] APR1000 PAFS Standard Design Development and EUR Certification Support

AWARDS & CERTIFICATES

International Atomic Energy Agency Fellowship, IAEA
Modeling and Computation of Multiphase Flows, ETH
International Marketing, Business and Intelligence, ATO
Full Academic Scholarship, KINGS

PERSONAL VENTURES

Nuclear Industry Association of Turkey, Board of Directors ☑

Turkish Chamber of Commerce in Korea, Co-Founder ☑

Hacettepe Rugby Club, Founder ☑